A Guide to the Policy Office: General Assembly Legislation of Governor Lawrence Douglas Wilder, 1990-1993.
Library of Virginia
- General Assembly Legislation, 1992.
  - House of Delegates Bills, 1992.
    - HB 39 (92) Charter - Town of Vinton, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - HB 40 (92) Charter - Town of Newcastle, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - HB 50 (92) Charter - Town of Clinchco, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - HB 51 (92) Charter - Town of Lebanon, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - HB 55 (92) Commission on Virginia Alcohol Safety Action Program, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - HB 62 (92) Christopher Newport College, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - HB 64 (92) Retail sales and use tax, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - HB 70 (92) Retail sales and use tax, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - HB 71 (92) Printed prescription drug forms, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - HB 72 (92) Charter - Town of Montrose, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - HB 73 (92) Charter - Affordable housing, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - HB 75 (92) Charter - Town of Buena Vista, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - HB 76 (92) Charter - Town of Buchanan, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - HB 86 (92) Waiver of extradition, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - HB 87 (92) Newspapers used for legal notices, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - HB 89 (92) Virginia Fish Passage Grant and Revolving Fund, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - HB 92 (92) Juvenile detention home and residential care facility commissions, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - HB 93 (92) Map coordinate values, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - HB 94 (92) Charter - City of Fairfax, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - HB 95 (92) Specialized Transportation Council, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - HB 96 (92) Relief of Masond Kovianporer, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - HB 101 (92) Charter - City of Martinsville, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - HB 106 (92) Charter - City of Virginia Beach, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - HB 109 (92) Charter - Town of Hillsville, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - HB 111 (92) Exemption from property tax - Family Resource Center, Inc., 1992. (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - HB 119 (92) Urban county executive form of government, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - HB 128 (92) Charter - Town of Leesburg, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - HB 131 (92) Relief of Nancy Ferris, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - HB 134 (92) Charter - City of Norfolk, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - HB 137 (92) Shareholder derivative suits, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - HB 139 (92) Minimum standards for local correctional facilities, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - HB 140 (92) Proration of tangible personal property tax, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - HB 142 (92) Sale of insurance by lending institutions, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - HB 143 (92) Placement of children for adoption by parent or guardian, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - HB 145 (92) Striking of civil cases from dockets, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - HB 146 (92) Trail exhibits, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - HB 147 (92) Use copies as evidence, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - HB 148 (92) Unauthorized release of animals, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - HB 151 (92) Dept. of Historic Resources, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - HB 155 (92) Local coal and gas road improvement tax for public education, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - HB 156 (92) Breaks Interstate Park, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - HB 157 (92) Local coal and gas road improvement tax, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - HB 159 (92) Clinch River as a scenic river, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - HB 160 (92) State Library and Archives, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - HB 161 (92) Admission into evidence of certificates of analysis, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - HB 162 (92) Firearms criminal background checks, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - HB 163 (92) Juvenile and Domestic Relations Courts - Transfers, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - HB 164 (92) Blood alcohol analysis, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - HB 168 (92) School boards, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - HB 169 (92) Route 501 bridge over the the Staunton River designated as Howard P. Anderson Bridge, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - HB 170 (92) Transient occupancy tax and food and beverage tax, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - HB 174 (92) Going out of business sales, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - HB 177 (92) Nottoway State Scenic River, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - HB 180 (92) Daycare programs, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - HB 181 (92) Insurable interests of charitable organizations, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - HB 182 (92) Dept. of Medical Assistance Services - Recovery of funds, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - HB 183 (92) Ethics in public contracting, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - HB 184 (92) Conduct of divorce suits, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - HB 185 (92) Land disturbing activities, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - HB 187 (92) Elections - Exceptions to purchasing and procurement laws, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - HB 188 (92) Regional jails, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - HB 189 (92) Cable television regulations, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - HB 190 (92) Attorney General / Consumer Finance Act, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - HB 191 (92) Rates of pilotage, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - HB 192 (92) Dept. for the Deaf and Hard of Hearing, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - HB 196 (92) Parole Board - Executive Director, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - HB 198 (92) Landfills - Separation of solid waste and disposal of leaves and grass, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - HB 199 (92) Driving on a suspended or revoked license, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - HB 201 (92) Surface water management are permit applications, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - HB 202 (92) State Corporation Commission, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - HB 204 (92) Group life insurance for health care providers in teaching hospitals, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - HB 206 (92) Southside Virginia Development Authority, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - HB 207 (92) Southside Virginia Marketing Council, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - HB 208 (92) Committee on District Courts, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - HB 209 (92) Road impact fees, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - HB 210 (92) Fire insurance - Replacement cost coverage, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - HB 212 (92) Immunization of children, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - HB 213 (92) Criminal penalties for state tax offenses, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - HB 214 (92) Motor fuels tax and motor carriers, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - HB 215 (92) Preservation of trial objections, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - HB 216 (92) Amber warning lights on motor vehicles, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - HB 217 (92) Appeal from juvenile courts, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - HB 220 (92) Human research, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - HB 221 (92) School property - carry weapons, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - HB 223 (92) Carrying concealed weapons, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - HB 224 (92) Campus police departments, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - HB 226 (92) Dept. of Transportation - Annual statements provided to county boards of supervisors, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - HB 227 (92) Property Owners' Association Act, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - HB 228 (92) Disposal of exhibits in civil cases, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - HB 229 (92) Issuance of bonds, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - HB 234 (92) Disposition of dead bodies, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - HB 236 (92) Public water supplies, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - HB 237 (92) Town relocation or change of boundary line, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - HB 238 (92) Exchange of information among states, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - HB 239 (92) Forfeiture of drivers license in drug conviction cases, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - HB 242 (92) Town treasurers to summon taxpayer, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - HB 243 (92) Probation and parole officers, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - HB 244 (92) Transmission of sentencing report, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - HB 245 (92) Dept. of Taxation, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - HB 248 (92) Virginia Voluntary Formulary, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - HB 249 (92) Actions to defeat profits from crime provisions, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - HB 250 (92) Local government accounts receivable - Penalty and interest, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - HB 251 (92) Denial of public assistance upon finding of fraudulent fees, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - HB 252 (92) Local board of public welfare / social services - Fraud units, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - HB 253 (92) Refunding bonds, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - HB 255 (92) Taking a child into custody, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - HB 256 (92) Unclaimed property, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - HB 257 (92) Musk thistle and curled thistle program, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - HB 258 (92) Enterprise Zone Act, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - HB 260 (92) Use of firearm on commission of a felony, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - HB 261 (92) Senate and House Ethics Advisory Panels, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - HB 262 (92) Board and Dept. of Medical Assistance Services, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - HB 263 (92) Bingo and raffles, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - HB 265 (92) Dept. of Aviation, Dept. of Motor Vehicles - Crash investigation teams and highway maintentance and construction, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - HB 266 (92) Utility diversion, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - HB 267 (92) Unified mapping systems, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - HB 268 (92) Superintendents and officers of regional jails, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - HB 272 (92) Professional corporations, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - HB 273 (92) Confederate cemeteries and graves, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - HB 276 (92) Robbery - Forfeiture of motor vehicle, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - HB 280 (92) Trust accounts for pre-need funeral contracts, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - HB 281 (92) Dept. of Economic Development, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - HB 282 (92) Governor's Economic Development Contingency Fund, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - HB 283 (92) Purchase of handguns by certian officers, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - HB 286 (92) Asbestos contractors and workers, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - HB 287 (92) Asbestos contractors and workers, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - HB 288 (92) Real Estate Board, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - HB 290 (92) Handicapped parking spaces, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - HB 292 (92) Design-build or construction management contracts, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - HB 293 (92) Virginia Freedom of Information Act - Executive or closed meetings, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - HB 295 (92) Virginia Freedom of Information Act, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - HB 296 (92) Underground Utility Damage Prevention Act, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - HB 297 (92) Virginia Freedom of Information Act, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - HB 298 (92) Flashing amber warning lights, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - HB 299 (92) Methods of payment for alcoholic beverages, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - HB 300 (92) Substance abuse advertising credits, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - HB 301 (92) Trustee of an established trust, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - HB 303 (92) Incorporation by reference of powers into a will or trust, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - HB 304 (92) Government Employees Deferred Compensation Plan Act, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - HB 305 (92) Electronic home incarceration, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - HB 306 (92) Family member assault, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - HB 308 (92) Sale and delivery of alcoholic beverages, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - HB 309 (92) School bus operators, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - HB 310 (92) Local taxes and fees on vehicles, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - HB 311 (92) Child support proceedings, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - HB 312 (92) Assignments of rents and leases, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - HB 313 (92) Deeds of trust, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - HB 314 (92) Real estate appraisers, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - HB 315 (92) Real estate appraisers, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - HB 316 (92) Disclosure of property owner membership lists, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - HB 318 (92) Furnishing commissioners of accounts with supplies, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - HB 322 (92) Anti-crime partnership program, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - HB 324 (92) Notaries - Conflict of interest, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - HB 325 (92) Urban enterprise zones, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - HB 326 (92) Possession or use of police radios in the commission of a crime, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - HB 327 (92) Board of Forestry, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - HB 328 (92) Emergency warning lights and operators of emergency vehicles, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - HB 330 (92) Purchase of handguns by certain officers, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - HB 331 (92) Elective officers - Right to consent or not to a nomination method other than a primary, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - HB 332 (92) Involuntary detention, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - HB 333 (92) Powers and duties of police force, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - HB 334 (92) Transportation of the mentally ill, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - HB 335 (92) Deposit of securities with the State Treasurer by insurers and health maintenance organizations, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - HB 336 (92) Use of toll facilities, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - HB 337 (92) HIV testing of persons charged with child molestation, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - HB 338 (92) Supervisor fees, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - HB 339 (92) Board of zoning appeals, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - HB 340 (92) Virginia Public Procurement Act - Alternate forms of security, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - HB 341 (92) Virginia Retirement System group insurance program, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - HB 342 (92) Regulation of architects, engineers, surveors and landscape architects, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - HB 343 (92) Fertilizer inspection, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - HB 344 (92) Home instruction courses, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - HB 345 (92) Licensure of school personnel2, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - HB 349 (92) Marginal notations and releases, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - HB 350 (92) Recordation and filing fees, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - HB 351 (92) Selling of consumer transaction information, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - HB 353 (92) Electronic voting machines and devices with memory cartridges, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - HB 354 (92) Corporations - Organization of cooperative associations, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - HB 355 (92) Designating the Shenandoah as a scenic river, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - HB 356 (92) Veterinary Medicine - Temporary licenses, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - HB 357 (92) Property Owners' Association Act, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - HB 358 (92) Mortgage Lender and Broker Act, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - HB 359 (92) Tax credit for rent reductions, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - HB 360 (92) Condominium Act, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - HB 361 (92) Virginia Graduate and Undergraduate Assistance Program, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - HB 362 (92) Uniform Statewide Buidling Code, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - HB 364 (92) Migrant labor camps, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - HB 367 (92) State Corporation Commission - Powers to punish for contempt, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - HB 369 (92) Damages in wrongful death actions, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - HB 370 (92) Community diversion programs, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - HB 372 (92) Garbage and refuse disposal, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - HB 374 (92) Workers' Compensation - Victims of sexual harassment, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - HB 375 (92) Use of recorded conversation as evidence in civil action, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - HB 376 (92) Bad checks, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - HB 379 (92) Audiology and Speech-language Pathology, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - HB 380 (92) Applications for absentee ballots, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - HB 381 (92) Submetering and energy allocation equipment, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - HB 382 (92) Possession of firearms while in possession of schedule I and II controlled substances, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - HB 383 (92) Investigations of diverted pharmaceuticals and treatment records, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - HB 384 (92) Distribution of drugs to minors, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - HB 387 (92) Restoration of driving privileges, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - HB 392 (92) Charter - Town of Lawrenceville, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - HB 394 (92) School Board employees - Criminal history record checks and fingerprinting, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - HB 395 (92) Compensation Board, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - HB 396 (92) Voting precincts and polling places, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - HB 400 (92) Restriction on amount of jury service, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - HB 401 (92) Personnel Advisory Board, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - HB 402 (92) Highway maintenance payments to municipalities, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - HB 403 (92) Tax credit for machinery and equipmnent for processing recyclable materials, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - HB 407 (92) Incompetence and guardianship proceedings, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - HB 408 (92) Real Estate Board, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - HB 411 (92) Access to criminal and DMV records by private police forces, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - HB 412 (92) Juvenile intake, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - HB 413 (92) Privilege to operate and register a motor vehicle, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - HB 418 (92) Retail sales and use tax base, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - HB 422 (92) Diagnostic pharmaceutical agents, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - HB 424 (92) Virginia Public Procedures Act and prompt payment, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - HB 425 (92) Personal property taxation of logging equipment, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - HB 426 (92) Virginia Debt Collection Act and prompt payment, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - HB 427 (92) Direct election of school board members, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - HB 429 (92) Alcohol Beverage Control Board, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - HB 430 (92) Bone marrow donor programs, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - HB 432 (92) Traffic infractions, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - HB 435 (92) Notice of confession of judgment provision, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - HB 436 (92) Fiduciary investments, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - HB 437 (92) Embezzlement of drugs, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - HB 438 (92) Pre-sentence reports, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - HB 440 (92) Special guest fishing licenses, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - HB 442 (92) Joint exercise of powers by counties, cities and towns, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - HB 444 (92) Revenue Stabilization Fund, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - HB 445 (92) Civil immunity for persons investigating and counseling lawyers impaired due to alcohol or substance abuse, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - HB 446 (92) Oil tax, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - HB 447 (92) Jail authorities, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - HB 448 (92) Design-Build contracts, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - HB 449 (92) Northumberland County highways as Virginia Byway, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - HB 451 (92) Public Offender offices, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - HB 452 (92) Child support enforcement, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - HB 454 (92) Child support, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - HB 455 (92) Fire insurance claims, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - HB 457 (92) Hunting deer with a rifle in Northampton County, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - HB 460 (92) Additional jurors, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - HB 463 (92) Medicaid New Drug Review Act, Virginia Medicail Drug Formulary, and Competitive Procurement of Drugs Program, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - HB 465 (92) Virginia Retirement System, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - HB 466 (92) Quorum requirements and voting by corporate directors, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - HB 467 (92) Share options, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - HB 472 (92) Common nuisance, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - HB 479 (92) Public defenders, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - HB 481 (92) Teacher grievance procedures, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - HB 488 (92) Management of groundwater, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - HB 489 (92) Energy conversion and cogeneration equipment, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - HB 491 (92) Accident and sickness insurance benefits, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - HB 492 (92) Southside Regional Airport at Blackstone, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - HB 493 (92) Motor vehicle insurance, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - HB 496 (92) Virginia Securities Act - Investigations, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - HB 497 (92) Retain Franchise Act, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - HB 498 (92) Insurance agents - Continuing education requirements, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - HB 499 (92) Birth-related Neurological Injury Fund, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - HB 501 (92) Comparison price advertising, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - HB 502 (92) Professional corporation and clinical nurse specialists, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - HB 503 (92) Pesticide Board, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - HB 505 (92) Local Agricultural and Forestral District Act, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - HB 507 (92) Mobile Home Lot Rental Act, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - HB 508 (92) Above ground storage facilities, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - HB 509 (92) Juvenile commitment hearings, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - HB 511 (92) Suits against prisoners, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - HB 512 (92) Credits for taxes paid in other states, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - HB 514 (92) Commonwealth's Attorneys' Services Council, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - HB 516 (92) Bank's duty to deny access to safe deposit boxes, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - HB 517 (92) Financial institutions - Fee or gift for purposes of influencing decisions, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - HB 519 (92) Civil jurisdiction of general district courts, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - HB 520 (92) Dept. of Corrections investigators, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - HB 523 (92) Manufacture, possession and use of fire bombs and explosives, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - HB 524 (92) Commitment of juveniles who are serious offenders, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - HB 527 (92) Virginia Asbestos NESHAP Act, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - HB 529 (92) Crab pots, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - HB 530 (92) Aquaculture, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - HB 531 (92) Disclosure by substitute judges, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - HB 532 (92) Portion of Rt 58 designated as The Edgar Baco Highway, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - HB 535 (92) Sanitary landfills, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - HB 541 (92) Campaign contributions and expenditures - Forms, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - HB 542 (92) Exempt property / security interests, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - HB 543 (92) Toxic Substances Information Act, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - HB 544 (92) Coal workers' pneumoconiosis claims, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - HB 545 (92) Examination of clerks, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - HB 546 (92) Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University to place real property in Fauquier and Loudoun Counties in an agricultural and forestral district, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - HB 547 (92) Virginia Winegrowers Advisory Board, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - HB 551 (92) Warning lights on school buses, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - HB 552 (92) Purchase of service handguns by officers, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - HB 553 (92) Virginia Scholars Program, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - HB 555 (92) Property tax relief for the elderly and handicapped, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - HB 566 (92) Local utility tax, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - HB 568 (92) Public safety employees and testing of blood-borne pathogens, 1992. (Box 42, Folder 1)